(Howard:)I know.
I wanna thank you
for taking time to see me.
(Hawking:)My pleasure.
(Hawking:)I enjoyed reading your paper
very much.
(Hawking:)You clearly have a brilliant mind.
(Howard:)I know.
(Hawking:)Your thesis that the Higgs boson
is a black hole...
(Hawking:)...accelerating backwards
through time is fascinating.
(Sheldon:)Thank you. It just... It came to me
one morning in the shower.
(Howard:)That's nice.
(Hawking:)Too bad it's wrong.
What do you mean, "wrong"?
(Hawking:)You made an arithmetic mistake
on page two.
(Hawking:)It was quite the boner.
No, no. But that can't be right.
l don't make arithmetic mistakes.
(Hawking:)Are you saying I do?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no. No, no, of course not.
(Sheldon:)It's just, I was thinking...
Oh, gosh, golly. I made a boo-boo.
(Sheldon:)And I gave it to Stephen Hawking.
(Hawking:)Great. Another fainter.